（忆往昔）
是我把路西法放出来的
I let Lucifer out.
我得把他再关进去
I got to put him back in.
好
Yes.
小萨姆已经不在这了
Sammy's long gone.
萨姆和米迦勒 路西法一起
Sam has been locked in the cage.
都关在牢笼里了
with Michael and Lucifer.
他的灵魂有问题 它消失了
It's his soul. It's gone.
抹去地狱的记忆我办不到
Can't erase Sam's hell,
但我可以将它隔离在屏障之外
but I can put it behind a wall.
继续调查 迪恩
Keep digging, Dean.
那你不跟我说说明白吗
So you're just gonna be cryptic, or…
是为了灵魂
It's about the souls.
我会救萨姆的
I will save Sam,
但前提是你不能插手
but only if you stand down.
- 你怎么了 小卡 - 我在交战状态
- What happened to you, Cass? - I'm at war.
我想来谈一笔简单的交易
I want to discuss a simple business transaction.
- 没别的 - 你想做交易
- That's all. - You want to make a deal.
跟我吗
with me?
是为了灵魂
It's the souls.
成千上万的灵魂
They're all inside me,
现在统统在我身体里
millions upon millions of souls.
天使之刃对我没用
Angel blade won't work,
因为我现在已经不再是天使了
because I'm not an angel anymore.
我是新的上帝
I'm your new God.
你们要卑躬屈膝
You will bow down.
向你们的主 也就是我 颂扬你们的爱戴
and profess your love unto me, your lord…
否则我就杀了你们
…or I shall destroy you.
（如今）
那么…
Well…
那好吧
All right, then.
这就行了吗…
This good or…
还是要我们五体投地
you want the whole forehead-to-the-carpet thing?
伙计们
Guys?
停下
Stop.
如果你们不是真心的 又有什么意义呢
What's the point if you don't mean it?
你们害怕我
You fear me.
不是爱 不是尊敬 只是害怕
Not love, not respect, just fear.
小卡
Cass …
萨姆 你还有什么可说的
Sam, you have nothing to say to me.
你从背后捅了我一刀
You stabbed me in the back.
平身
Get up.
小卡 得了 这不是你
Cass, come on. This is not you.
你认识的卡西迪奥已经不在了
The Castiel you knew is gone.
那你要怎样 杀了我们吗
So what, then? Kill us?
你可真是个勇敢的小东西啊
What a brave little ant you are.
你清楚你无力还击
You know you're powerless.
你不敢再对我动手
You wouldn't dare move against me again.
因为那没有用
That would be pointless.
所以我没必要杀了你
So I have no need to kill you.
至少现在不用
Not now.
况且
Besides…
你们背叛我之前
once, you were my favorite pets,
也曾是我最爱的宠物
before you turned and bit me.
- 你到底是谁 - 我是上帝
- Who are you? - I'm God.
如果你们安分守己
And if you stay in your place,
就可以在我的王国里生存
you may live in my kingdom.
如果你们反抗 我就灭了你们
If you rise up, I will strike you down.
感觉不是很舒服吧 对吗 萨姆
Not doing so well, are you, Sam?
我没事
I'm fine.
你说你会治好他的 你保证过的
You said you would fix him. You promised!
前提是你们不插手 可你们没有
If you stood down, which you hardly did.
对我的仁慈心存感激吧
Be thankful for my mercy.
我本可把你扔回那个牢笼里
I could have cast you back in the pit.
小卡 别这样 这真是疯了
Cass, come on, this is nuts.
你还能改变这一切 求你了
You can turn this around, please!
为了你好 我希望这是你们最后一次见我
I hope, for your sake, this is the last you see me.
萨姆 你没事吧
Sam, you okay?
萨姆
Sam.
你们要明白
Understand…
如果你追随拉斐尔
if you followed Raphael,
如果你们反抗我
if you stood against me,
我肯定会惩罚你们
punishment is certain.
你们无处躲藏
There is nowhere to hide.
其他人
The rest of you.
我们的父亲已经离开很久了
Our father left a long time ago.
这很难熬
That was hard.
我曾以为我们需要的是自由意志
I thought the answer was free will.
但我现在明白了
But I understand now.
你们需要一个强大的领导
You need a firm hand.
你们需要一个父亲
You need a father.
现在我就是你们的父亲
And I am your father now.
孩子们 你们要听话
Be obedient, children…
否则这就是你们的下场
or this will be your fate.
这是新的纪元
It is a new day,
对于人间和天堂都一样
on earth and in heaven.
欢庆吧
Rejoice.
[邪恶力量 第7季第1集]
加油
Come on.
加油 宝贝
Come on, baby!
你是在修理她还是在乱喊乱叫啊
So, you fixing her or primal screamin'?
谢谢
Thanks.
萨姆怎么样了
How's Sam?
他还没醒 但还活着
He's still under, but alive.
好的
Yeah.
咱们的新上帝怎么样了
What about God part deux?
我现在四处打探消息
I got all kinds of feelers out.
目前还没什么发现
So far, diddly.
你到底在找什么啊
And what exactly are you looking for?
- 问题就在这儿 - 什么问题
- Exactly. - What?
奇迹 群体产生幻觉
Miracles, mass visions,
还是玉米饼上出现小风衣
trench coat on a tortilla?
我也不知道我在找什么
I don't know what I'm looking for.
没事 他会露面的
Yeah, well, he'll surface.
就算我们找到
So, say we do us out.
升级版上帝的踪迹
where new and improved flew off to.
怎么了
Yeah.
那到时候我们怎么办
The hell we plan to do about it?
我不知道 鲍比
Well, I don't know, Bobby.
我跟你一样毫无头绪
I got no more clue than you do.
我都不知道到上哪本书里找资料 迪恩
I don't even know what books to hit for this, Dean.
想想办法嘛
Well, figure it out!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这事书里肯定没有
This ain't in no book.
就算你稍微探个头 小卡就会灭了你
If you stick your neck out, Cass steps on it.
你知道我要干什么吗
So, you know what I'm gonna do?
干什么
What?
我要把这车修好
I'm gonna fix this car…
因为这是我力所能及的
Because that's what I can do.
我能把她修得好好的
I can work on her till she's mint.
等萨姆醒来之后
And when Sam wakes up,
不管他是副什么德行
no matter what shape he's in,
咱们也能帮他恢复正常
we glue him back together, too.
那是咱们该做的
We owe him that.
我挺你
I'm with you.
嗨 迪恩
Hey, Dean.
你…恢复得不错嘛
Wow, you're, uh, walking and talking.
是啊
Yeah!
我…
I, uh…
生活能自理 完全好了
Put on my own socks … whole nine.
那还真是…
Well, that's, um…
我是说…
I mean, uh, you…
- 你真的没事了吗 - 对啊
- You sure you're okay? - Yeah.
头还有点疼 不过基本恢复了
My head hurts a little, but…Basically.
- 真的吗 - 我也觉得不可思议
- Seriously? - Look, man, I'm as surprised as you are,
- 但我真的没事了 - 那就好
- but, yeah, I swear. - Good.
既然你没事
No reason putting a gift horse.
- 我们也该知足了 - 对啊
- under a microscope, right? - Yeah.
小卡那边怎么样了
So what happened with Cass?
过来帮我一起修车吧
Why don't you come help me with the car,
- 边修边跟你讲 - 好的
- and I'll fill you in? - Okay.
（宁静教堂 信仰上帝 他就在我们身边）
许多人宣扬他们所谓的生活方式
Plenty speak for them and their so-called lifestyle …
各路媒体 好莱坞
Media, Hollywood.
雷帝嘎嘎满口都是爱情和金钱
Lady Gaga won't shut up for love or money.
实在可笑
Yeah, funny.
但正因如此 我们才要高声呐喊
But that's why we raise our voices.
反对他们所谓的婚礼和葬礼
and picket their so-called weddings and their funerals.
总得有人来传达上帝的旨意
Someone has to speak for God.
谁说你传达的就是上帝的旨意了
And who says you speak for God?
你错了
You're wrong.
我对性取向毫不关心
I am utterly indifferent to sexual orientation.
但是
On the other hand…
我不能对你这样的伪君子纵容姑息
I cannot abide hypocrites like you, reverend.
好了 别闹了 朋友
Okay, fun's over, friend.
在替我传达旨意之前 你先告诉各位信徒
Tell your flock where your genitals have been.
你喜欢男人还是女人
before you speak for me.
你到底是谁
And who the heck are you?
我是上帝
I'm God.
以我的名义撒谎之人 将被自己的榫舌噎死
And he who lies in my name shall choke on his own false tongue.
被自己的恶言出卖
and his poisonous words shall betray him.
因为我是主
For I am the Lord…
你们的上帝
Your God.
卡西迪奥
Castillo.
卡西
Cass.
（松林商场 加州 萨克拉门托）
不不不
No, no, no.
不不不 这不可能
No, no, no, no. This can't be happening.
萨姆
Hey, Sam?
你在这下面打盹呢
What are you, taking a nap down here?
- 好像有小卡的消息 快来 - 好
- It's Cass, we think. Come on. - Yeah.
这就来
Coming.
约二百名宗教领袖暴毙身亡
Sudden deaths of some 200 religious leaders.
此事件正在调查之中
are currently under investigation.
梵蒂冈方面尚未发表声明
The Vatican has yet to issue a statement,
但部分民众已将其称为「神迹」
but some are already calling this an act of God.
我们都看到他了
We all saw him …
没蓄胡须 没穿长袍
No beard, no robe.
他很年轻
He was young…
而且 还很性感
And … and sexy.
他穿了件风衣
He had a raincoat.
据悉
Believed to be targeted hits.
三K党多位高层遇刺
high up in the white-supremacy organizations,
联调局认为这一白人至上的组织已被迫解散
the FBI now believes the Ku Klux Klan has been forced to disband.
这我倒没意见
Can't argue with that one.
今天早些时候
Freak lightening strikes.
共鸣启迪中心在一场大火中被烧毁
on the heels of the fire that burned down.
随后又被诡异的闪电击中
the center for vibrational enlightenment earlier today.
据发言人表示 「这一惨剧是
Said a spokesman, "This tragedy represents.
新时代励志演说家史上最大的损失「
the largest loss in new-age motivational speaker history."
励志演说家
Motivational speakers?
是啊
Yeah.
现在的小卡没也不比以前的那位更懂反讽
I'm not sure new Cass gets irony any better than old Cass.
当然了 以前的小卡
Course, old Cass…
不会为了表明立场就毁了麦迪逊广场
wouldn't smite Madison Square Garden just to prove a point.
他陷得太深了
He is off the deep end of the deep end.
根本没打算停手
And there's no slowing down.
那怎么办 再试着跟他谈谈吗
So, what? Try to talk to him again?
萨姆
Sam.
迪恩 咱们只能跟那家伙谈谈
Dean, all we can do is talk to the guy.
他可不是什么家伙
He's not a guy.
他是上帝 而且很生气
He's God, and he's pissed.
上帝私设公堂 你可别去拦着他
And when God gets righteous, you get the hell out of the way.
- 你没读过圣经吗 - 大概如此
- Haven't you read the Bible? - I guess.
小卡不会回来了
Cass is never coming back.
他骗了咱们 利用了咱们
He has lied to us, he used us,
他毫不在乎地就推到了你脑袋里的墙
He cracked your gourd like it was nothing.
没必要谈了
No more talk.
- 咱们已经跟他费尽口舌了 - 好
- We have spent enough on him. - Okay.
把管钳递给我
Hand me that socket wrench.
（田纳西州 坚信上帝）
不少人称其为「奇迹般的康复」
After what many are calling a miracle healing.
我们请来了卫生部通讯员
Here with me, health correspondent.
罗伯·路易斯基
Rob Lewitski.
路易斯基 看你能讲出什么道道来
Educate me, Lewitski.
你好 克劳力
Hello, Crowley.
你貌似很紧张
You look stressed.
该死
Bollocks.
这么说
So…
我露陷了
The jig is up.
- 你找到我了 - 我一直掌握着你的行踪
- You found me. - I never lost you.
你这些小伎俩没什么用
These scratches … they're all useless.
人家总得挣扎两下嘛
Still, can't blame a girl for trying.
灭我之前想不想喝两口
You fancy a drink before you smite me?
不想
No.
你喜欢速战速决 对吧
You like to bend 'em right over, do you?
来吧
Let's go.
我不会杀你 克劳力
I'm not going to kill you, Crowley.
我留着你还有用处
I have plans for you.
- 什么用处 - 接下来这么办
- What's that? - Here's our new arrangement …
我饶你不死
I let you live.
- 你重新做回地狱之王 - 但是呢
- You return to your post as King of Hell. - But?
但是灵魂的去处由我说了算
But I choose where each soul goes.
- 但是 - 我来掌控灵魂的去向
- But … - I control the flow,
给你剩多少 你就拿多少
and you take whatever I give you.
我想你想拿大头吧
I take it you intend to keep the lion's share.
那么
So…
你的意思是地狱要缩编了
What you're saying is hell is being downsized.
我本可以把地狱彻底消灭
I would have done away with it completely,
不过我得有东西来要挟我的敌人
but I need a threat to hold over my enemies.
我们要让米迦勒一直待在路西法的牢笼里
And we need to keep Michael in Lucifer's cage.
没错
Right.
我想这事我们…没商量的余地吧
I gather this is not say a, uh, negotiation.
- 没有 - 那我非常乐意接受…
- No. - Then I graciously accept…
老大
Boss.
保持联系
I'll be in touch.
迪恩
Dean?
鲍比
Bobby?
她看上去还算不错
She's looking good… Considering.
还算
Considering?
我都能当职业选手了
I should do this professionally.
那…
So…
最近注意萨姆没
seen Sam lately?
怎么了
Yeah, why?
什么
What?
痛快点说出来
Well, spit it out.
那孩子怎么可能还没倒下
How is that kid even vertical?
小卡可是把那堵墙推到了
I mean, Cass broke his damn pinata.
我知道
I know.
我理解当时在实验室他怎么还能帮上忙
I mean, I get how he came to help us, back at the lab.
- 肾上腺素 - 没错
- Adrenaline. - Sure.
那现在呢
But now?
他说他没事了
Well, he says he's okay.
怎么可能
How?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只祈求上帝他真的没事
I just pray to God it's true.
我们得换个新说法了
We need to come up with a new saying for that.
说真的 鲍比 看我们过的这日子
Seriously, though, Bobby. I mean, look at our lives.
我们还能经受多少打击
How many more hits can we take?
所以如果萨姆说他很好 那就是好
So if Sam says he's good, good.
你相信吗
You believe that?
我信
Yeah.
不
No.
你想知道为什么吗
You want to know why?
因为我们一直走背字
Because we never catch a break,
这次怎么会这么幸运
so why would we this time?
可是 或许就在这事上 能走点运
But just … just this one thing, you know?
我还没那么蠢
But I'm not dumb.
我不会把期望放太高
I'm not gonna get my hopes up.
再挨当头一棒子
just to get kicked in the daddy pills again.
感觉如何 小子
Well, how you feeling, sport?
好得没话说
Can't complain.
很好
Great.
什么事
What's the word?
有家出版社大概在一小时前
Well, a publishing house literally exploded.
发生了爆炸
about an hour ago.
死的人真的太多了
Guys, the body count is really getting up there.
我们得做点什么了
We got to do something.
我们要做的就是找到那个狗娘养的
What we got to do is hunt the son of a bitch.
不幸的是 我的神枪没了 所以…
Unfortunately, I lost my God gun, so…
还有什么别的天堂武器吗
I mean, is there some kind of heavenly weapon?
或许用巴尔萨泽从那个天使兵器库
I mean, maybe something out of that Angel Arsenal.
偷的什么东西
that Balthazar stole?
肯定有东西能对付得了他
There's got to be something that can hurt him.
他是上帝 萨姆
He's God, Sam.
没东西伤得了他
There's nothing.
不过有个人或许可以
But there might be someone.
不
No.
不 不
No, no!
别这样
Come on!
别这么惊讶
Don't act so surprised.
我的新老大甚至会因为
My new boss is gonna kill me for.
跟你们这帮人说话而杀了我
even talking to you lot.
我们没往你的脏脸上捅刀子你就偷乐吧
You're lucky we're not stabbing you in your scuzzy face,
- 你个混… - 等等
- you piece of … - Wait, wait, wait.
- 什么新老大 - 卡西迪奥 你们这群白痴
- What new boss? - Castiel, you giraffe.
是你的老大
Is your boss?
是每个人的老大
Is everybody's boss.
你觉得当他发现
What do you think he's gonna do.
我们在密谋逆反 他会怎么做
when he finds out we've been conspiring?
你们是打算密谋点什么吧
You do want to conspire, don't you?
不 我们只想要你帅气的站在那里
No, we want you to just stand there and look pretty.
我在听
Listening.
我们需要一道符咒
We need a spell.
来捆绑死神
To bind death.
捆绑 控制死神
Bind? Enslave death?
你在开玩笑吗
You having a laugh?
- 路西法干过 - 因为他是路西法
- Lucifer did it. - That's Lucifer.
咒语不分人
A spell's a spell.
你真的觉得你们能够驾驭那样的马力
You really believe you can handle that kind of horsepower?
你们这是痴心妄想
You're delusional!
各路神仙里 只剩下死神
Death is the only player on the board left.
还有PK小卡的能力
that has the kind of juice to take Cass.
他俩都会把我们碾成豌豆泥
They'll both mash us like peas.
我为什么要帮一个自杀式行动
Why should I help on a suicide mission?
听着
Look…
你真的希望小卡掌控整个宇宙吗
you really want Cass running the universe?
请施舍点吧
Some help, please?
拜托了 帮帮我
Please? Help?
请施舍点吧
Some help, please?
上帝保佑你 先生
God bless you, sir.
你是名真正的信徒
You're a true believer.
人们都说我充满愤怒
People say I'm wrathful.
可我只惩罚骗子和那些背叛我的人
But I only punish liars and those who forsake me.
我是个公平的上帝
I am a just God.
您说什么
Excuse me?
你看
See?
我的天
Oh, my God.
我看得见了
I can see!
你的脸
Your face.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
你犯错了
Mistake.
太晚了
Too late.
放我们出去
Let us out.
让我们出来
Let us through.
放我们出去
Let us out.
不
No.
有人吗
Hello?
克劳力寄来的
It's from Crowley.
谁今晚想给死神来个五花大绑
Well, who feels like hog-tying Death tonight?
反正长命百岁也没那么好
Old age is overrated anyhow.
东西都准备得差不多了
Well, we got most of this stuff,
但有几样东西还得去跑个腿
But we're gonna have to make a run for a few things.
比如说
Like?
比如「借于神迹 封于水晶」
Like "An act of God, crystallized forever."
这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我认为是指真正的水晶
Thinking it means an actual crystal.
当闪电以合适的角度打在沙地上
See, lightning strikes sand at the right angle,
它就能自动结晶为完美的形状
it crystallizes into the perfect shape of itself.
闪电 神迹
Lightning … act of God.
正解
Jenga.
得去找块闪电岩
You got yourself a fulgurite.
还得找块大的来
We're gonna need a biggie.
我猜猜 稀罕到可遇不可求吧
And let me guess … rare.
我找到了一个拍卖记录
I found the records of an auction.
中标者距咱这儿这儿九小时车程
Winning bidder lives about nine hours from here.
抱歉 你有芥末酱吗
Excuse me. You got any Grey Poupon?
芥末酱 不是吧
Grey poupon? Seriously?
我脑子里就蹦出这玩意儿了
It's what popped in my head.
我不想伤了你俩的
I don't want to hurt you.
真心的
Really.
手里有枪的可是我 孩子
I'm the one with the firearm, son.
我当然知道
I get that.
好了
Okay.
不错 好极了
Yeah. Good.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
这是威斯医生和夫人
Uh, so this is Dr. and Mrs. Weiss.
你们好
Hi.
对不起
Sorry.
我找到那个神迹什么的了
I found the God thingy.
好了 我们就开始仪式吧
Well, let's light this candle.
不客气
You're welcome.
[咒语]
来了吗
Hello?
死亡骑士
Death?
开什么玩笑呢
You're joking.
抱歉 死亡骑士 不是看上去那样的
I'm sorry, death. This isn't what it seems.
看上去你们把我绑起来了
Seems like you bound me.
我们有充分理由 好吗
For good reason, okay?
你就听我们把话说完
Just, uh, hear us out.
要来点儿油炸泡菜片吗
Fried pickle chip?
他们可是全州最棒的
They're the best in the state.
你觉得我就这么好打发吗
That easy to soothe me, you think?
我猜 是跟萨姆的幻觉有关吧
This is about Sam's hallucinations, I assume?
什么
What?
抱歉 萨姆 每个人只能竖一次墙
Sorry, Sam. One wall per customer.
现在给我松绑吧
Now unbind me.
不行
We can't.
目前不行
Y-yet.
这事不会有好结果的
This isn't going to end well.
我们想让你终结了上帝
We need you to kill God.
什么
Pardon?
终结上帝
Kill God.
你没听错
You heard right.
阁下
Your…Honor.
你们凭什么认为我办得到
What makes you think I can do that?
是你告诉我的
You told me.
那为什么我要那么做呢
Why should I?
因为
Because…
我们要你做 现在你得听我们的
We said so, and we're the boss of you.
不过是客气地请你做
I mean…Respectfully.
难以置信
Amazing.
小卡
Cass.
我本不想杀你们 但如今
I didn't want to kill you, but now…
你杀不了我们
You can't kill us.
我对你的旧情已被你抹得干干净净 迪恩
You've erased any nostalgia I had for you, Dean.
死亡骑士是我们的小弟了
Death is our bitch.
就算是上帝动手 我们也死不了
We ain't gonna die, even if God pulls the trigger.
他们果然是令人讨厌的低等生物 不是吗
Annoying little protozoa, aren't they?
上帝
"God"?
在我看来 你更像是变异了的天使
You look awfully like a mutated angel to me.
你的皮囊正在融化 你马上就要爆炸了
Your vessel's melting. You're going to explode.
不 我不会的
No, I'm not.
等我搞定了手上的事 我自会修复好我自己
When I've finished my work, I'll repair myself.
你认为你办得到是因为你认为
You think you can because you think.
你只不过是无法负荷这么多灵魂 对吗
you're simply under the weight of all those souls, yes?
但那还不是最严重的问题
But that's not the worst problem.
在炼狱中有着比那些灵魂更加古老的东西
There are things much older than souls in purgatory,
你当时也一并吞下了
and you gulped those in, too.
无关紧要
Irrelevant.
我自能控制他们
I control them.
暂时罢了
For the moment.
等一下 更古老的东西是什么
Wait … uh, what older things?
早在上帝创造天使和人类之前
Long before God created angel and man,
他创造了第一只野兽
he made the first beasts …
利维坦（圣经中象征邪恶的一种海怪）
The Leviathans.
利维坦
Leviathans?
我个人觉得他们其实挺可爱的
I personally found them entertaining,
但他却担心他们会毁了整个世界
But he was concerned they'd chomp the entire petri dish,
所以他把它们锁了起来
so he locked them away.
不然你们认为他创造炼狱是要干嘛呢
Why do you think he created purgatory?
就是为了隔离那些狡慧而又危险的东西
To keep those clever, poisonous things out.
而如今卡西迪奥已经吞下了他们
Now Castiel has swallowed them.
他成为了这些古老之物和你们世间的唯一隔膜
He's the one thin membrane between the old ones and your home.
够了
Enough.
你真是个愚蠢至极的兵蛋子
Stupid little soldier you are.
为什么这么说
Why?
因为我敢开启那被他尘封的大门吗
Because I dared open a door that he shut?
他人在哪儿呢
Where is he?
我恪尽职守 替他打点好他的地方
I did a service, taking his place.
恪尽职守
Service?
是指平息那场小争斗吗
Settling petty vendettas?
不止
No.
我一次又一次地收拾残局
I'm cleaning up one mess after another …
毫无私心
Selflessly.
真是位慈善家
Quite the humanitarian.
你又知道什么
And how would you know?
说真的 你究竟是什么
What are you, really?
一个苍蝇拍吗
A flyswatter?
我认为 至少注定要拍死你
Destined to swat you, I think.
除非我先下手为强
Unless I take you first.
这家伙 还真是够王婆卖瓜自卖自夸的
Really bought his own press, this one.
拜托了 卡西
Please, cass.
我认识上帝
I know God,
而您呢 不是那个料
and you, sir, are no God.
行了 你们俩就别废话了
All right, put your junk away, both of you.
听着 你怎么喊他都成 快杀了他就好
Look, call him what you want. Just kill him now!
好吧 行
All right. Fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们现在可以开打了吗
Shall we kickbox now?
我有预感 某人即将命丧我手
I had a tingle I'd be reaping someone very, very soon.
别担心 不是你们
Don't worry … not you.
他还挺着急
Well, he was in a hurry.
没错 我正是为此
Yes, that's exactly.
再次参加竞选
why I'm running again …
我有义务保护我的选民
to save my constituents.
免受对手们那些邪恶政策的摆布
from the Godless policies of my opponents.
你说得再好不过了
Couldn't have said it better myself.
先生
Sir?
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
我来找参议员
I'm here to see the Senator.
事由是…
Um, regarding?
滥用职权
Abuse of power.
什么
Excuse me?
我做的才不是小事
I am not petty.
我要惩罚一个借我之名
I'm punishing a woman.
肆虐贫穷和绝望的女人
who causes poverty and despair in my name.
我将你们的利益置于首位
I put your needs first.
难道你不明白吗
Don't you understand?
你们所有人都听着
All of you.
我是比我父亲更好的上帝
I am a better God than my father.
我要如何才能让你们明白
How can I make you understand?
闭嘴 迪恩
Shut up, Dean.
我不是专门负责给你收拾烂摊子的
I'm not here to tie your shoes every time you trip.
我早就警告过你那些灵魂的事情
I warned you about those souls how long ago?
你们有足够的时间阻止那个傻瓜
Long enough to stop that fool.
而现在可好
And here we are again,
你们的小星球又即将遭受屠杀
with your little planet on the edge of immolation.
我很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry.
好吗 我一直忙着拯救这个星球
All right? I've been trying to save this planet.
也许你该去警告个更好的人
So maybe you should find somebody better to tip off.
也许我该去拯救个更好的星球
Maybe I should spend my effort on a better planet.
我玩得很开心
Well, it's been amusing.
等等 等…等等
Wait, h-hold on, hold on.
你能给我们一些提示吗
Just … can you give us something?
你…你对我们必须有那么
You … you have to care a little bit about.
一点点在乎吧
what happens to us.
我其实根本不在乎
You know, I really don't.
但我的确觉得那个小天使很傲慢
But I do find that little angel arrogant.
很好 就这么说吧
Great. Let's go with that.
你们唯一的希望
Your only hope is.
就是立刻让他把所有东西
to have him return it all to purgatory.
还回炼狱
quickly.
我们需要一扇门
We need a door.
你们需要的所有东西那个实验室里都有
You have everything you need at that lab.
带他回到那 强迫他放弃神力
Get him to return there and compel him to give up the power.
强迫
Compel?
自己想办法
Figure it out.
但那扇门只在月蚀的时候开启
But that door only opens in the eclipse.
而那已经结束了
And that's over.
我会再做一扇
I'll make another.
周日早上3点59分
3:59 Sunday morning,
破晓之前
Just before dawn.
记住要准时
Be punctual.
别感谢我
Don't thank me.
把你的烂摊子收拾好
Clean up your mess.
再绑我一次试试
Try to bind me again,
你动手之前就会没命
you'll die before you start.
顺便说一句 泡菜片不错
Nice pickle chips, by the way.
不
No.
你需要配点咖啡吗
You want some coffee with that?
不用 某些地方现在是晚上六点呢
No. It's 6:00 p.m. somewhere.
我们得出发了
We got to hit the road.
我们怎么可能赶在该死的凌晨3点59分前
I mean, how are we supposed to get Cass to that lab.
把小卡带到实验室
by friggin' 3:59 a.m.?
我们不用
We don't.
「我们不用」是什么意思
What do you mean, "We don't"?
我们无法把马带到水边
I mean, we can't bring the horse to water,
我们也无法逼马喝水
and we can't make it drink.
何必自欺欺人呢
Why fool ourselves?
迪恩 听着
Dean, look,
我知道你认为小卡已经走了
I know you think that Cass is gone …
- 因为他的确走了 - 他没有
- It's 'cause he is. - He's not!
他还在内心的某个角落 迪恩
He's in there somewhere, Dean.
我知道
I know it.
- 不 你不知道 - 不 我不知道
- No, you don't. - No, I don't.
但我自己也有段时间魂不守舍
But, look, I was pretty far gone sometimes myself,
而你从来没放弃过我
and you never gave up on me.
没错 而事实证明
Yeah, and it turns out.
你还是一如既往的开诚布公
that you're about the same open book as you've always been.
幻觉 你不是吧
Hallucinations? Really?
我还得从死亡骑士那儿听来
I got to find out from Death?
那我该怎么做
What was I supposed to do?
不如坦白吧
How about not lie?
不如告诉我
How about tell me.
你那堵墙上都爬了些什么烂七八糟的玩意
that you've got crazy crap climbing those walls?
为什么
Why?
你无能为力
You can't help.
你最近的麻烦事够多的了
You got a lot of pretty severe crap swinging your way lately,
而…而我认为…
and … and I thought …
怎么了 我何必去破坏
What? I thought why burst.
你仅存的美好愿望呢
the one good bubble you had left?
我能控制住
It's under control.
什么
What?
到底什么需要你控制住
What, exactly, is under control?
我能辨别真实与幻觉
I know what's real and what's not.
- 萨姆 - 迪恩
- Sam. - Dean,
我们可以对付完小卡再议此事
look, we can debate this once we deal with cass.
你知道我要怎么对付吗
Yeah, you know how I'm gonna deal?
我会大吃一顿 喝点小酒
I'm gonna stuff my piehole, I'm gonna drink,
看点亚洲卡通黄片
and I'm gonna watch some asian cartoon porn,
整得像世界要爆炸了一样
and act like the world's about to explode.
因为的确如此
because it is.
这是在开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
「一名身着风衣的男子血洗
"Massacre at the campaign office of an incumbent senator.
现任参议员竞选办公室「
by a trench-coated man."
这有安全监控录相
There's security footage.
我想召唤小卡已经…不太可能了
Well, I think reaching Cass is, uh…out of the cards.
卡西迪奥
Hey, Castiel.
也许这根本没用 听着
Maybe this is pointless. Look…
我不知道你是否还会有一点在乎
I don't know if any part of you even cares,
但…我仍然视你为自己人
but, um, I still think you're one of us,
在你的内心深处
deep down,
无尽的潜意识深处 但是…
I mean, way, way, way off the reservation, but…
到明天凌晨 此事还能挽救
Look, we still have till dawn to stop this.
让我们帮你
Let us help.
求你了
Please.
你关了再说
Only if you turn that off.
萨姆
Sam?
小卡
Cass.
我听到了你的召唤
I heard your call.
你们得帮我
I need help.
血浆要找对
We need the right blood.
过道走到底有个小罐子
there's a small jar end of the hall,
在供给品橱里面
s-supply closet.
了解
Got it.
迪恩
Dean?
怎么 还要什么
What, you need something else?
不
No.
我很愧疚
I feel regret,
对你 和我对萨姆做的事
about you and what I did to Sam.
你该愧疚
Yeah, well, you should.
如果还有时间 如果我还有力气
If there was time, if I was strong enough,
我会马上治好他
I'd … I'd fix him now.
我只希望死前能弥补一下
I just wanted to make amends before I die.
好啊
Okay.
有用吗
Is it working?
会让你觉得舒服点吗
Does it make you feel better?
不
No.
你呢
You?
一点也不
Not a bit.
我知道 看起来都很傻 是不是
I know. It all seems so silly, doesn't it?
你好 萨姆
Hi, Sam.
好久不见
Long time, no spooning.
你不在这儿
You're not here.
你在地狱啊
You're in hell.
你说得非常对
Now, that you're right on.
挂肉钩 锁链
Meat hooks…Chains…
和你
You.
不是真的
It's not real.
只是我的脑子在释放记忆
It's just my brain leaking memories from the cage.
因为那道墙崩溃了
'cause of the wall breaking down.
仅此而已
That's all.
非常好 你的小理论
That's very good, your little theory.
它是错的
It's wrong.
萨姆 不是你变得不正常
Sam, this isn't you going guano.
是你周围的一切
Everything else is.
什么
What?
一切
Everything…
从你跳出囚笼的那一刻起
from the second you sprung out of that lock box.
那不可能
That's impossible.
不 逃出来是不可能的
No. Escaping was impossible.
我不得不说
I have to say,
我想这是我最好的折磨手段
I think this is my best torture yet …
让你以为你自由了
make you believe that you're free and then.
然后突然摘下遮眼布
yank the wool off of your eyes.
你从没跑出去过 萨姆
You never left, Sam.
你还在囚笼里
You're still in the cage.
和我在一起
with me.
挺住
Hang in there.
再等几分钟
Just a couple of minutes.
萨姆去哪儿了 时候到了
Where's Sam? It's go time.
萨姆
Sam?!
见鬼
Damn it.
已经可以了
That's good enough.
好 站起来 小卡
Okay, step right up, Cass.
我很抱歉 迪恩
I'm sorry, Dean.
小卡
Cass?
他身体都冷了
He's cold.
还有呼吸吗
Is he breathing?
没
No.
也许天使不需要喘气
Maybe angels don't need to breathe.
他死了 迪恩
He's gone, Dean.
该死的
Damn it.
小卡 你个死孩子
Cass, you child.
为什么不听我的
Why didn't you listen to me?
小卡
Cass?!
好了
Okay.
All right.
真不舒服
That was unpleasant.
把他弄起来 小心
Let's get him up. Easy, there.
我复活了
I'm alive.
貌似是
Looks like.
我震惊了
I'm astonished.
谢谢你们 你们两个
Thank you … both of you.
我们也就是想拯救地球而已
We were mostly just trying to save the world.
我很羞愧
I'm ashamed.
我做得太过了
I really overreached.
你以为呢
You think?
我会想办法向你赎罪的
I'm gonna find some way to redeem myself to you.
好的 饭要一口一口吃 走吧
All right, well, one thing at a time. Come on.
我们离开这里 走吧
Let's get you out of here. Come on.
我说真的 迪恩
I mean it, Dean.
好的 没问题
Okay. All right.
咱们去找萨姆 好吧
But let's go find Sam, okay?
你们得马上逃
You need to run now!
我挡不住他们
I-I can't hold them back!
挡住谁
Hold who back?
他们留在我体内了
They held on inside me.
迪恩 他们太强大了
Dean, they're so strong.
- 到底是谁 - 利维坦
- Who the hell! - Leviathan!
我扛不住他们
I can't fight them.
快跑
Run!
走 去找到萨姆 去找到萨姆
Go! Go get Sam! Go get Sam!
太迟了
Too late.
小卡
Cass?
小卡 他消失啦
Cass is … he's gone.
他死啦
He's dead.
现在我们接管了
We run the show now.
这将会非常非常有趣的啦
Oh, this is going to be so much fun.